<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">swecha</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>
    
    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item >Home</item>
        <item >Events</item>
        <item >Photos</item>
        <item >Projects</item>
        <item >News</item>
        <item >Techdays</item>
        <item >About us</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@drawable/ic_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_people</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_photos</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_communities</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_pages</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_whats_hot</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_about</item>
    </array>
    
    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>
    <string name="about1">Swecha was founded in 2005 as an organisation to support the Swecha project, it is now a vibrant community of software users, students, academicians and software professionals/developers determined to provide quality software built on the guidelines of free software development model. </string>
    <string name="about2">Swecha aims at providing global software solutions to the local people with the Free Software development model by working together with the community of developers and users all over. The prime objective of Swecha OS is to provide a complete computing solution to a population that speaks and understands only Telugu.</string>
    <string name="about3">The project aims at bridging the gap between the computer technology that exists predominantly in English and the Telugu-speaking community of India. The project also aims at providing a framework for development and maintenance of Free Software projects taken up by the community.</string>
    <string name="about4">Swecha is a project aimed at coming out with a localised version of GNU/Linux in Telugu. The target users of the distro being the entire community that is a prey of the digital divide. This project helps in coming out with a solution for the digital divide and allows the possibility of digital unite becoming a reality.</string>

</resources>
